<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>2231puppy.tech</title>
    <link>https://2231puppy.tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 2231puppy.tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 14:36:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2231puppy.tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>KiCad on Android: The PCB Design Setup No One Asked For</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/personal-setup/kicad-on-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 14:36:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/personal-setup/kicad-on-android/</guid>
      <description>What life? Why exist? How live? Why do I mean? If you find yourself asking asking these big questions, you&amp;rsquo;re probably a robot. No offense, ChatGPT. A real human would be asking much more important questions of themselves:
How the heck do I run KiCad on Android? Because there&amp;rsquo;s nothing more important in life than running an open-source EDA suite on your smartphone.
Whether or not that assumption is correct doesn&amp;rsquo;t really matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Fidget - Update 3</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-3/</guid>
      <description>Yes, I know it&amp;rsquo;s been almost a full year since my last update. Sorry - I&amp;rsquo;ll try to not let that happen again!
Hey everyone! My last post on the E-Fidget was a quick status update on version 1. Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve gone through 2 other versions of the main E-Fidget and two versions of its little sibling, the E-Fidget Lite.
Version 1 of the E-Fidget Lite Version 2 of the E-Fidget Lite The most recent version of the E-Fidget (The E-Fidget Lite V2, if you&amp;rsquo;re keeping count) is the most successful version so far!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Fidget - Update 2</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-2/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce that the E-Fidget&amp;rsquo;s schematic and layout are complete! I&amp;rsquo;ve sent the gerber files out to a PCB manufacturer, and I&amp;rsquo;ve ordered all the parts. I&amp;rsquo;ll have a full ordering tutorial soon! In the meantime, here&amp;rsquo;s a preview: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Fidget - Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>The KiCad v6 source and gerbers can be found here. The board will run CircuitPython. Full instructions will be on this page soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Fidget - Update 1</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/update-1/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;ve been working a little on the schematic for the E-Fidget, and it&amp;rsquo;s going great! Here&amp;rsquo;s what I have: (For those wondering, this is KiCad 6 with the Dracula color scheme on macOS.)
There are some changes that I have planned, like switching out the transistors for FETs (Thanks for suggesting that, you know who you are!). Cleaning up the schematic is also on my agenda. In the meantime, I&amp;rsquo;ve started on the layout, but I don&amp;rsquo;t think that&amp;rsquo;s ready to share quite yet (It&amp;rsquo;s ugly and not 10% done).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-Fidget - Intro</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/projects/e-fidget/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello again! Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on a project I&amp;rsquo;m calling the E-Fidget, a battery-powered fidget spinner for lazy people. Here&amp;rsquo;s the rundown:
How it works Essentially, there&amp;rsquo;s going to be some vibration motors, arranged in a circle. In the center, there&amp;rsquo;ll be a button to make the motors turn on and off very rapidly, in a circular motion. The idea is that this will emulate a spinning motion, while still working in your pocket!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Started a Blog</title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/i-started-a-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 19:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/posts/i-started-a-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hiya, internet! I&amp;rsquo;m 2231puppy/Micha, a teen programmer, game developer, aspiring digital musician, pixel artist, and vegan. I&amp;rsquo;ll be blogging about all of those things at one point or another. Here, you&amp;rsquo;ll find my rants, notes, discoveries, and more! Check back soon for a new post!
Until next time!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://2231puppy.tech/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2231puppy.tech/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there 👋, I&amp;rsquo;m 2231puppy/Micha I&amp;rsquo;m an aspiring fullstack developer I commissioned this beautiful art of my cats from @TheColorfulKayak
I think JS should be illegal 99% of the time (TS is the GOAT!) 3D printing is awesome. I want to learn low level development. Linux &amp;gt; macOS &amp;gt; Windows (for programming at least)
Skills: TS / Svelte / SvelteKit // TailwindCSS // Python / FastAPI // Godot
🔭 I’m currently working on a cool multiplayer combat-based MMO (yes, it&amp;rsquo;s gonna take a while) 🌱 I’m currently learning relational database schemas.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
